[MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOG BARKING]
[MUSIC CONTINUING]
And that was like 1981. 1981.
And we talked over the phone [PAUSE] many months
before we ever met. Yeah -- . Before we met in person
because I remember saying to my friend who introduced us
I say what is that look like
It's obviously social media
He said Well it looks like a van Walker
It sound like. Okay --
[MUSIC CONTINUING]
And one of our sports editors
Uhh [FILLERS]. Came to me and said. Listen the person you know
We normally have covering a dog show
she can't do it this year.
Something came up. Would you like to do it.
And. I was like maybe it changed me some different.   You know we always.
I grew up in Maryland we always and how big land yard lots of dogs
I was like I'd be crazy
I a challenge something kind of fun to do I'd love to do that
I said on one condition.
[PAUSE]
I said there's a lot of space the Territory cover
I need an excellent cold water to help me get quotes and other things so I can pick my own person
And she said are you keeping a way in the world.
I said I want a kick since you're lou lou
[LAUGHING]
So---. So sound like really
[MUSIC CONTINUING]
Well you've got to prep for. You do.
you've got the prep for it the way you prep to cover your Super Bowl or covering the World Series
Hmm mm.
I know all your players
you know you have to look at [Ahh]-- you've
just like dogs those sports there are stats
Hmmm..hmmm
you got to look at who your top hounds are
who your top dogs are
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It is the mom and pops like they are the breeder owner handler and then
there are the very fancy
You know literally how much can you spin to show this stuff
How much you do
You can spin
you know just bare bones minimum
or literally upward toward a million they have private jets
They have the top trainers that are very expensive
They -- ah they spared no expense to show the dog.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
When all said and done
was it come down to change
this dog on the day
You know it's whoever is the top dog that really [pause] pulls it all together
In that moment all this sense of like has some dogs
you just got the head showing so well and they're great
The previous night but when it comes to best in show is the finale
somehow maybe they're tired the fatigue or
[INTERRUPTION: or a dog in] there or a dog waiting
Like I said 24 hours before dog
Or dog that you have --
it showed you earlier in the day obviously that you thought did pretty good
Yeah. all of a sudden it's stacks.
That's what they call it when it dawns.
Yeah that's correct and they --
But the whole slate pose really.
[INTERRUPTION : pose really beautifully ]
Like a statue
And looks like a statue like it was I should agree
It looks like the cover of the Westminster program
It looks perfect
I mean -- all
And you'll look at your watch you'll say
[BELL CLING] Dog on a day
[BELL CLING] It's like a boom
I mean bang
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You don't have the alligator show
[LAUGHING]
rIght where you don't have the duck show
[ANIMALS SOUNDS]
They do a cat show
[CAT MEOWS ]
They don't have the goat show
[ANIMALS SOUND]
[LAUGHING]
DOGS. it's all about dogs
[DOG BARKING]
[MUSIC ENDS]